Contact

- (+91-8866144982
- manas.soumya@gmail.com
- 168/517, SRI GURU NAGAR, Lingipur, Nuagaon, BBSR, ODISHA 751002

Education

2005 - 2009

Arena Animation Academy

Bachelor in computer application (AAASP)

2002 - 2005

Utkal University

Bachelor of Arts (B.A)

2000 - 2002

Sishuanant Mahabidyalaya

+2 in Arts

Skills

Web Technologies:

HTML5, Css3, Bootstrap

CMS:

WordPress, Shopify, Square Space

Design:

Photoshop, Figma, Illustrator

Others:

MS-Word, MS-Excel, MS-Power Point, jQuery.

Test Execution:

Responsive Testing, Cross Browser Compatibility.

Flowchart Tools:

Draw.io

Language

English

Hindi

MANAS **RANJAN**

Sr. Frontend Developer | UI/UX Designer

About Me

More than 8 years of working experience as Frontend Developing. having knowledge as UI/UX Designer with Bootstrap, Shopify, Square Space and WordPress integration and various tools. Currently associated with Devs In India Pvt Ltd, Ahmedabad as Senior Frontend Developer.

Experience

Devs In India Pvt Ltd

Aug 2020-Present

Sr. Frontend Developer & UI Designer

- . Create & slice Ui design layout to user-friendly web pages/portals .
- . Convert Ui design to WordPress
- . Maintaining and improving website.
- . Optimizing applications for maximum speed
- . Help SEO team for optimizing sites.

GIT Pvt Ltd 2014 - 2019

Sr. Frontend Developer & UI Designer

- . Create & slice Ui design layout to user-friendly web pages/portals .
- . Convert Ui design to WordPress
- . Maintaining and improving website.
- . Optimizing applications for maximum speed
- . Create Ui/Ux for App and website/portal.

I-Serve System Pvt Ltd

2013 - 2014

Sr Frontend Developer

- . Create & slice Ui design layout to user-friendly web pages
- . Convert Ui design to WordPress
- . Maintaining and improving website.
- . Optimizing applications for maximum speed

P & K Infocom Pvt Ltd

2011 - 2013

Frontend Developer

- . Create & slice Ui design layout to user-friendly web pages
- . Convert Ui design to WordPress
- . Maintaining and improving website.
- . Optimizing applications for maximum speed

Project Details

Form700

url: https://www.form700.com.au

Aesthetik

url: https://aesthetik.com.au/

UFS

url: https://www.ufsdirect.com.au/

Perfect Property

url: https://perfectproperty.com.au/

Kartaway

url: https://www.kartaway.com.au/

Vintage Cellar

url: https://cellarpress.vintagecellars.com.au/

Plant Rich Catering

url: https://plantrichcatering.com.au/

Watch Time

url: https://www.watchtime.com.au/

Dr. Umed

url: https://www.drumedcosmetics.com.au/

Gold State

url: https://portal.goldstate.com.au/

Boyd Studio

url: https://boydstudio.com.au/

Brisbane Home Loan

url: https://brisbanehomeloan.com.au/

Cappah Group

url: https://cappahgroup.com.au/

Deaf Children Australia

url: https://www.deafchildrenaustralia.org.au/

Disave

url: https://disave.com.au/

Engage

url: https://engage.itcc.net.au/

The Market - First Choice Liquor

url: https://themarket.firstchoiceliquor.com.au/

Global Insurance Solutions

url: https://www.globalinsurancesolutions.com.au/

Hermitage Homes

url: https://portal.hermitagehomes.com.au/

Horizon Solar

url: horizonsolarpower.com.au

Express Commercial Kitchens

url: https://expresscommercialkitchens.com.au/

Express Laundry

url: https://www.laundryequipmentmelbourne.com.au/

ITECAU

url: itecau.com.au

ITHEA

url: https://ithea.vic.edu.au/

Laser Machines

url: lasermachines.com.au

Seven Stallion

url: https://sevenstallion.com/